scbwi.org 2016-12-19

# SCBWI | Privacy Policy

* * *

All SCBWI information is the intellectual property of the SCBWI and is to be used only with written permission by the SCBWI Headquarters.

All email addresses and other contact information on the SCBWI website are intended for personal use by SCBWI members wishing to connect with other members or their Regional Advisors. Generic email addresses posted are for informational use only and may not be used for any solicitation or advertising. Unsolicited advertising or emails of any kind sent to any SCBWI member including, but not limited to, Regional Advisors, Assistant Regional Advisors, Illustrator Coordinators and any employee of SCBWI, is prohibited. Parties engaged in solicitation in violation of this policy may be subject to legal action as well as immediate termination of the violator's SCBWI membership. 

Unless we have your express permission, SCBWI does not share your contact information with anyone, other than reputable contractors doing work for SCBWI (such as the mailing house that handles our Bulletin). Such contractors are never allowed to retain or use your contact information except for the purpose of the work we've assigned them. 

**Types of personal information we keep in our databases**

We keep in our databases your name, contact information, billing information, and publishing history, including your current publisher and literary agent. 

**How we use your information**

We use your personal information to provide and improve our services, for billing, for identification of authentication of members (for member programs and services), to contact members and for internal research. We also periodically send emails to member groups notifying you of various SCBWI events. If you do not wish to receive such notifications, you may choose to opt out either by calling us at 323-782-1010 or clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any SCBWI email. 

**We don't share your information with third parties without permission**

When asked, unless you have advised SCBWI in writing to the contrary, inform people of your agent's name and contact information. SCBWI does not share your other personal information with anyone, other than reputable contractors doing work on its behalf, unless you've expressly permitted SCBWI to do so.  An example of a reputable contractor is the mailing house that handles our Bulletin.  Such contractors are never allows to retain or use your contact information except for the purpose of the work SCBWI has assigned them. 

##  Children's Privacy  

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, SCBWI does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 is allowed to provide any personal information to or on SCBWI. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at scbwi@scbwi.org

**Changes**

SCBWI may periodically update this policy. SCBWI will notify you about significant changes in the way it treats your information by sending a notice to the primary e-mail address specified in your membership record or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

**Questions**

For any questions about this Privacy Policy call 323-782-1010 or by mail at: 4727 Wilshire Blvd., Suite 301, Los Angeles, CA 90010
